Izzy: Morning, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Hi… I… Hi… Hello. Good morning.
Izzy: Is this your local coffee shop?
Ben: Yeah. My school is really near here.
Izzy: Oh yes, Tensquare School.
Ben: Yeah.
Do you know it?
Izzy: Yeah, I do.
Carla: What would you like, Izzy? Your usual?
Ben: Izzy.
Izzy: Yes, please. How are you, Carla?
Carla: I’m good. And you?
Izzy: I’m OK.
Carla: How’s the job?
Izzy: Good! It’s long hours, but I like it.
Ben: Uh… are you two friends?
Izzy: Yeah. I come here a lot. I live very near here.
Ben: Really?
Izzy: Yeah. How’s the course?
Ben: Good, but…it’s really hard work.
I don’t like the teacher very much.
Izzy: Andre…
Ben: Do you know him?
Izzy: Yeah. He’s… difficult.
Nice to see you again, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Izzy? Um… Oh, sorry.
Erm, I… um… Do you…
Izzy: Do you want to go out sometime?
Ben: Me?
Izzy: You.
Ben: Yeah.
Izzy: OK.
Here’s my number.
Call me.
Carla: Have a biscuit.